beezmap.com 2011-11-27

# Beezmap - Privacy Policy

**Any inquiries related to the functions of the BeezMap.com website should be directed to BeezMap using the contact information provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.**

BeezMap is committed to protecting the privacy of the users of the BeezMap.com site. Please read the Statements below which describe in detail the kinds of data that are collected by the site, the manner in which it is stored, and the purposes it is used for. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Notification of changes to this policy will be posted on this page.

Collection of Your Personal Information

On this site, we collect and store your email address, gender, and demographic data via registration and use of the site, as well as your chosen username and password. BeezMap automatically receives and records in our server logs information from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp.

If you order items from the BeezMap, we will collect your address and phone number; this information will be provided to third-party suppliers to complete your order. The third-party suppliers will also collect your credit card details, which will be encrypted to protect confidentiality and will not be stored by BeezMap.

Personal information that you provide to BeezMap is stored and processed in the United States. If you are providing this information from outside the United States, please note that U.S. law may not provide the same protections for your personal information that your home country may provide.

Use of Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. Different websites can each send their own cookies to your browser if your preferences allow it. Your browser only allows a site to access the cookies it sent to you, not the cookies sent by other sites. You can configure your browser to accept or reject cookies. All browsers are different, so go to the help section of your browser to find out how to do this.

None of your secure information, such as credit card and payment details, username, or password, is collected by these cookies. However, we use the cookies to collect the following information: search engine referrals, product browsing, site navigation, and purchasing. All information collected by these cookies is sent to BeezMap by secure connection. All information will be retained as long as necessary.

Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

As stated above, we collect information from you via registration, server logs, and cookies. You may also choose to post information to other areas of the site. BeezMap retains user-posted content (such as messages or other information you post to the site) as long as it deems necessary.

We link user-posted information to the other information we collect and use this data to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base. We do this in order to improve our service and build a better site for you to use.

Communications from BeezMap and Third Parties

BeezMap reserves the right to communicate with you at the email address you provide with regard to updates to the BeezMap.com site, changes of policies, and your use of the site. This does not limit your right to 'opt out' of receiving communications from BeezMap, associated companies, or other companies of a marketing nature.

Should you decide to 'opt out' (at registration) of receiving information and marketing updates from BeezMap, you will not be contacted for this purpose.

During registration, we may offer you the opportunity to opt-in to receive mailings from companies not associated with BeezMap. Should you choose to opt-in, some or all of your personal data may be shared with other companies, and BeezMap may not control the use of your email address and the content of email you may receive.

Should you wish to change your registration status at anytime to either opt out or in of the above, please send an email to [account@beezmap.com](mailto:account@beezmap.com). Note however that if you opt in to receiving communications from other companies and subsequently wish to opt out of receiving such communications, you will need to contact them to remove yourself from their mailing lists, in addition to contacting BeezMap.

Security of Your Personal Information

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information, although we cannot guarantee it. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems located in controlled facilities, and we limit access to those computers.

Other Disclosures

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights; to protect the rights, property, or safety of other persons; to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us; or in connection with an actual or proposed corporate transaction or insolvency proceeding involving all or part of the business or assets to which the information pertains.

Links to Other Sites

This privacy policy applies only to information collected on this site. The site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by BeezMap. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the site and to read the privacy policies of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information.

Third Party Information

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)[here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)[and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Contact Information

We welcome your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you believe that we have not adhered to this Statement, or if you have any other questions, please contact us by email. [inquiries@beezmap.com](mailto:inquiries@beezmap.com)
